(melancholy music)
♪ I hear the clock, it's 6 a.m. ♪
♪ I feel so far from where I've been ♪
♪ I got my eggs and my pancakes too ♪
♪ I got my maple syrup,
everything but you ♪
♪ I break the yolks and
make a smiley face ♪
♪ I kinda like it in my brand new place ♪
♪ I wipe the spots off of the mirror ♪
♪ Don't leave the keys in the door ♪
♪ I never put wet towels on
the floor anymore 'cause ♪
♪ Dreams last for so long ♪
♪ Even after you're gone ♪
♪ And I know you love me ♪
♪ And soon you will see ♪
♪ You were meant for me ♪
♪ And I was meant for you ♪
(melancholy music)
♪ I called my mamma,
she was out for a walk ♪
♪ Consoled a cup of coffee,
but it didn't wanna talk ♪
♪ So I picked up the paper,
it was more bad news ♪
♪ More hearts being broken,
more people being used ♪
♪ Put on my coat in the pouring rain ♪
♪ I saw a movie it just wasn't the same ♪
♪ 'Cause it was happy or I was sad ♪
♪ And it made me miss
ya oh so bad 'cause ♪
♪ Dreams last for so long ♪
♪ Even after you're gone ♪
♪ And I know you love me ♪
♪ And soon you will see ♪
♪ You were meant for me ♪
♪ And I was meant for you ♪
♪ I go about my business, I'm doing fine ♪
♪ Besides what would I say
if I had you on the line ♪
♪ Same old story, not much to say ♪
♪ Hearts are broken every day ♪
(melancholy music)
♪ I brush my teeth, I
put the cap back on ♪
♪ I know you hate it when
I leave the light on ♪
♪ I pick a book up and
turn the sheets down ♪
♪ And take a deep breath
and a good look around ♪
♪ Put on my pjs and hop into bed ♪
♪ I'm half alive but I feel mostly dead ♪
♪ I try and tell myself it'll be alright ♪
♪ I shouldn't think
anymore tonight 'cause ♪
♪ Dreams last for so long ♪
♪ Even after you're gone ♪
♪ And I know you love me ♪
♪ And soon I know you will see ♪
♪ You were meant for me ♪
♪ And I was meant for you ♪
♪ Yeah, you were meant for me ♪